Guide to the Frank Fragale Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
Frank Fragale Collection
1941-1958
ARS-0007
Frank and Josephine Fragale
11 linear ft. (17 boxes)
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound Stanford University Libraries Stanford, California 94305-3076
The Fragale collection consists primarily of scores and recordings, and secondarily of programs, photographs, articles and materials on Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde?s libretto.
Access
Collection is open for research. Listening appointments may require 24 hours notice. Contact the Archive Operations Manager.
Biography / Administrative History
Frank Fragale (1894-1955), a native of Sciara, Italy, received his music education at the Bellini conservatory in Palermo. He continued his studies in New York with Julius Gold, a teacher he felt very indebted to. In 1915 he joined the San Francisco Symphony and Opera as a bass-clarinetist. He combined a performing and composing career. His most important compositions were the Fantasia for cello and piano which won him an honorary recognition at the Third International G. B. Viotti Competition, and his opera Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, with a libretto by W. Erich. The opera was premiered in 1953 at the Berkeley Garfield Theater with Earl Bernard Murray and Marsden Argall as conductors of the orchestra and chorus. The performers were volunteers from the Berkeley Opera Workshop and the local Musicians Union.
Scope and Content of Collection
The Frank Fragale Collection consists mainly of scores. These are divided in three groups: the opera, Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde (111 folders), chamber music (61 folders) and orchestral music (21 folders). Most of the materials in the collection relate to his opera, such as the sixteen photographs. Among the libretto materials are versions in English and Italian. The ten programs range from 1941 to 1958. In addition there are twenty-two articles, six reel to reel tapes, fifty-five instantaneous lacquer discs, and five commercial discs documenting Fragale?s work.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series: I. Scores. II. Libretto materials. III. Programs. IV. Photographs. V. Articles and newspaper clippings. VI. Miscellaneous documents. VII. Recordings.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Fragale, Frank, 1894-1955; Operas.
Container List
- Scores
  - Act I. Scene 1. Prelude. Orchestral score (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Act I. Scene 1. Prelude. Instrumental parts (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Act I. Scene 1. Prelude. Piano reduction (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Act I. Scene 1. Prelude. "Ah..." Vocal parts (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Act I. Scene 1. Prelude. Vocal parts. "Ah..." Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Act I. Scene 2. Choral score, "Ah..." (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Act I. Scene 2. Vocal parts, "Ah..." (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Act I. Scene 2. Vocal parts. "Ah..." Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Act I. Scene 3. Trio: mother, woman, old man. "Thank you sir." Vocal score (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Act I. Scene 3. Trio: mother, woman, old man. "Thank you sir." Vocal score. Transparencies. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Act I. Scene 4. Utterson aria. "Oh Jekyll, once you did confide in me." Vocal score (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Act I. Scene 4. Utterson aria, "Oh Jekyll, once you did confide in me." Vocal score. Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Act I. Scene 6. Jekyll aria, "The hour is striking." Vocal score. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Act I. Scene 6. Jekyll aria, "The hour is striking." Vocal score. Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Act I. Scene 6. Chorus, "Change from Jekyll to Hyde." Choral score. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Act I. Scene 6. Chorus, "Change from Jekyll to Hyde." Choral score. Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Act II. Scene 1. Ballet. Choral score, water damaged (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Act II. Scene 1. "Watch them dance." Vocal score. Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Act II. Scene 1. Off stage chorus, "Who cares when life is such a whirl." Vocal parts (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Act II. Scene 1. Off stage chorus, "Who cares when life is such a whirl." Vocal parts. Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Act II. Scene 1. Duet, Jack and Ada. "You are all the world to me." (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Act II. Scene 1. Trio: Ada, Jack and Utterson. "Hyde the villan he must fall." Vocal parts (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Act II. Scene 1. Trio: Ada, Jack and Utterson. "Hyde the villan he must fall." Vocal parts. Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Act II. Scene 2. Chorus, "Change from Jekyll to Hyde." Choral score. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Act II. Scene 2. Chorus, "Change from Jekyll to Hyde." Choral score. Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Act I, complete. Piano reduction (working score) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Act II, complete. Piano reduction (working score) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: flute. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: flute II and piccolo. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: flute III and piccolo. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: oboe I. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: oboe II. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: English horn. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Clarinet I in b flat. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Clarinet II in b flat. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Bass clarinet. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Bassoon I. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Bassoon II. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Bassoon III and contrabassoon. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Horn I in f. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Horn II in f. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Horn III in f. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Horn IV in f. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Trumpet I in b flat. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Trumpet II in b flat. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Trumpet III in b flat. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Trombone I. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Trombone II. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Trombone III. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Tuba. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Timpani. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: Triagnle, cassa, tamburo. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: harp. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin I. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin II. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: viola. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violoncello. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bass. Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: flute I (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: flute II and piccolo (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: flute III and piccolo (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: oboe I (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: oboe II (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: English horn (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: clarinet I (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: clarinet II (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bass clarinet (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bassoon I (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bassoon II (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bassoon III and contrabassoon (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: horn I in f (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: trumpet I in b flat (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: trumpet II in b flat (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: trumpet III in b flat (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: trombone I (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: trombone II (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: trombone III or bass (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: tuba (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin I, stand 2 (first stand missing) (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin I, stand 3 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin I, stand 4 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin I, stand 5 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin I, stand 6 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin II, stand 1 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin II, stand 3 (stand 2 missing) (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin II, stand 4 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violin II, stand 5 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: viola, stand 2 (stand 1 missing) (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: viola, stand 2 (stand 1 missing) (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: viola, stand 3 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: viola, stand 4 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violoncello, stand 2 (stand 1 missing) (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violoncello, stand 3 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: violoncello, stand 4 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bass, stand 2 (stand 1 missing) (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: bass, stand 3 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: harp (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: triangle, cassa, tamburo, stand 1 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: triangle, cassa, tamburo, stand 2 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: triangle, cassa, tamburo, stand 3 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Instrumental part of complete opera: timpany (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Opera fragments (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Bound orchestral score, Act I (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Bound orchestral score, Act II (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Bound piano reduction of complete opera (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Bound piano reduction of complete opera (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Bound piano reduction of complete opera (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Bound piano reduction of complete opera (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Bound piano reduction of complete opera (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Bound piano reduction of complete opera (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Bound orchestral score, Act I (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Bound orchestral score, Act II (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Allegretto giocoso in b flat major, for woodwind quintet (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Allegretto grazioso in c major, for woodwind quintet (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Allegro moderato in f major for piano (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Andantino calmo in c major for piano (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Andantino calmo in c major for woodwind quintet (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Andante tranquillo in c major for piano (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Angora Lake. For woodwind quintet (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Angora Lake. For woodwind quintet. Transparencies (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Apprezzamento. For piano (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Barcarolle. L'amour Venitienne. For piano (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Battelino. For soprano and piano (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Clarinet Rhapsody. For clarinet, and piano (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Danza Drammatica. For flute and piano (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Danza Drammatica. For clarinet and piano (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Danza Drammatica. For alto sax and piano (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Danza Drammatica. For tenor sax and piano (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Danza Drammatica. For violin and piano (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Danza Drammatica. For viola and piano (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Danza Drammatica. For piano solo (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Danza Drammatica. For xylophone and piano (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Fantasia. For violoncello and piano (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Fantasia. For brass ensemble (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Fuga a 4 voci. For piano (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Fuga in a flat major. For flute, clarinet, violin, cello and piano (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Incipient. For three bassoons (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Lipona. For violin and piano (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Lipona. For viola and piano (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Lipona. For violoncello and piano (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Lipona. For flute, oboe and bass clarinet (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Lipona. For two clarinets and bass clarinet (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Lipona. For woodwind quintet (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Memoirs du lac. For woodwind trio (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Memoirs du lac. For woodwind quintet (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Nocturne in d flat major. For piano (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Nocturne in f major. For piano (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Passacaglia. For piano (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Primavera. For piano (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Primavera. For oboe, clarinet and piano (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Primavera. For violin, violoncello and piano (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Rondino. For four flutes (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Rondo. For piano (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Shaniselle. For woodwind trio (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Shaniselle. For woodwind quintet (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Soliloquy. For piano (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Soliloquy. For violoncello and piano (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Sonatina. For piano (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Sonatina. For piano. Transparencies (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Sprightly Flight. For four winds (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - String quartet and horn. Score (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - String quartet and horn. Parts (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Tango for piano (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Tango for piano. Transparencies (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Themavaria. For string quartet (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Themavaria. For string quartet. Transparencies (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Theme with variations. For piano. Working score (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Woodwind quintet in b flat major (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Woodwind quintet in c major., Negative of score (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Woodwind quintet in c major. Parts (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Fragments, various parts (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Clarinet Rhapsody. Score (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Clarinet Rhapsody. Parts (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Crickets. Scores (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Crickets. Score. Negative (pages missing) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Crickets. Parts (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Danza Drammatica. Score (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Danza Drammatica. Parts (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Fantasia for solo violoncello and orchestra. Score (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Fantasia for solo violoncello and orchestra. Parts (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Fantasia for solo violoncello and orchestra. Parts. Negatives (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Nocturne. Score and parts (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Passacaglia. Score, copy1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Passacaglia. Scores copies 2 and 3 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Passacaglia. Score copy 4 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Passacaglia. Score. Negative (pages missing) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Passacaglia. Parts (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Passacaglia. Scores for wind band (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Primavera. Score (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Suite. Score (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Suite. Score. Mirror image (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Suite. Parts (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Libretto materials
  - Typed libretto by W. Erich (three copies) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Typed libretto by W. Erich. Revised version (six copies) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handwritten libretto by W. Erich. Italian version (two copies) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Typed libretto by W. Erich. Italian version (two copies) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Index of acts and scenes (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Libretto fragments (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Annotated book: Strange case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Annotated booklet: Luella Forepaugh and George F. Fish. Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde of a mis-spent life.copyright 1897 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Programs
  - Ten programs ranging from 1941 through 1958. Four undated or with incomplete dates. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Photographs
  - Fourteen photographs (three different prints plus multiples) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Autographed portrait of Monteux, Pierre, 1875-1964, oversize (Box 6, Folder 2)
    "To Frank Fragale with my best wishes for his success as a composer and with my sincere affection." Note attached: "I read your opera with interest and when I come I will tell you certain things." Sincerely P. Monteux
  - William Derrell Bond, stage director for the performance of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Artlices and newspaper clippings
  - Twenty-two articles ranging from 1941 through 1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous documents
  - Miscellaneous documents, oversize (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Promotional leaflet of Murray, Earl; Handwritten notes on the radio program Standard Hour; Envelope addressed to Frank Fragale
- Recordings
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde I (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde II (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde III (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. HydeMay 13, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Transformation scene from Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde -- Brass Ensemble and a cappella choir
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Intermezzo: Ballet (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Battelino for soprano and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Trio from oboe duet. Intermezzo for oboe, clarinet and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Sprightly Flight for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lipona and Danza Drammatica, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Intermezzo for oboe, clarinet and piano and Sprightly Flight for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Intermezzo for oboe, clarinet and piano. Sprightly Flight for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    San Francisco Symphony woodwinds
  - Sprightly Flight for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs du lac for flute, oboe and clarinet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Memoirs du lac for flute, oboe and clarinet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Memoirs du lac for flute, oboe and clarinet. Lipona for flute, oboe and clarinet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Memoirs du lac for flute, oboe and clarinet. Lipona for flute, oboe and clarinet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Memoirs du lac for flute, oboe and clarinet. Lipona for flute, oboe and clarinet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Danza Drammatica. Lipona, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Danza Drammatica for violin and piano., Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Danza Drammatica for violin and piano. Lipona, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lipona for flute, oboe and clarinet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Battelino for soprano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Sprightly Flight for flute, oboe, clarinet and bassoon. Intermezzo for oboe, clarinet and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Sprightly Flight for for flute, oboe, clarinet and bassoon. Intermezzo for oboe, clarinet and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Danza Drammatica for alto sax solo, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Radio program, Standard Hour. PassacagliaApril 16, 1950, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Fantasia for cello and piano part I, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Fantasia for cello and piano part II, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Fantasia for cello and piano part III, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Woodwind quartet and horn, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Lipona for violin and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Lipona for violin and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Woodwind quartet and horn, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Woodwind quartet and horn, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Memoirs du Lac for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Aria, Dr. Jekyll. Aria, Utterson, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Aria, Utterson, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Aria, Utterson, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Duet, Jack/Ada. Trio, mother/woman/oldman, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Trio, mother/woman/oldman, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Trio, mother/woman/oldman, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Act I, part 1. Act II, part 3, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Act I, part 2. Act II, part 2, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. Act I, part 3. Act II, part 1, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Passacaglia, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Caprice Drammatico for alto sax solo, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde., Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Lipona for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Lipona for woodwind quintet, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 50)